(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
YUZUKI CHOCO. The school nurse at the Underworld Academy. Is incredibly popular among the students, with the boys in particular coming to get checked up all the time. Loves sweets, and often gets into trouble for having them stored on her desk.
「好きですか」の難題に、
To the difficult question of "Do you like me?",
笑顔で返すしかできない。
I can only respond with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように、
As if teased by a devil,
私の答案を君は待っている。
you're waiting for my answer.
放課後の教室に、
In the classroom after school,
君だけを残す時間が好き。
I like the time when only you are left.
二人きりになっても、
Even if we're alone together,
許されるわけになるでしょう？ ねえ。
it'll be permissible, right? Hey.
きっとあの頃のように、
Surely, like back in those days,
隣を歩けないのは、
the reason I can't walk beside you is...
待つ制服に、
the waiting school uniform,
揺れる白衣。
and the swaying white coat.
それが二人の距離だから。
Because that's the distance between us.
熱くなるほど幼い、
My heart, which is as immature as it is passionate,
心がバレちゃわないように、そっと。
I hope it doesn't get found out... softly.
君にとっての先生になるふりして
Pretending to be a teacher to you,
担う、秘密のクラス。
I take on this secret class.
「好きですか」の難題に、
To the difficult question of "Do you like me?",
笑顔で返すしかできない。
I can only respond with a smile.
まるで悪魔にからかわれたように、
As if teased by a devil,
私の答案を君は待っている。
you're waiting for my answer.
甘い恋で仕立て、
Tailored with sweet love,
あるがままにしてあげよう。
I'll leave it as it is for you.
去る制服と、揺れる白衣。
Departing uniform and swaying white coat.
ふとした言葉も傷つけてしまう。
Even casual words can end up hurting.
失うものが何もない
Having nothing left to lose
無邪気な瞳で苦しめないで。
Don't make me suffer with those innocent eyes.
君のテストに先生さえも
Even the teacher, for your test,
答えられない 言葉に詰まる。
Can't answer; I'm at a loss for words.
「好きだよ」と全部捨てて、
“I love you,” throwing everything away,
抱き寄せてしまいたいのに。
even though I want to pull you close.
そんな強い心じゃいられない。
I can't maintain such a strong heart.
私の答えに罰をつけて。
Put a mark of punishment on my answer.
これでいい。君のために
This is fine. For your sake,
そう決めたのに。
I had decided that, and yet...
去る制服へ、靡く白衣。
To the departing uniform, the fluttering white coat.
思わず君を引き止める。
I instinctively hold you back.
「好きですか」の難題に、
To the difficult question, “Do you love me?”
許されない答案を書いた。
I wrote an unpardonable answer sheet.
君の将来を縛るだけの
One that only binds your future,
独り善がりな、恋の約束。
a self-satisfied promise of love.
ただ君の悲しむ顔を、
I just didn't want to see
もう見送らなくていいなら。
your sorrowful face anymore.
たとえ悪魔と呼ばれてもいい
Even if I'm called a demon, it's fine
甘くとろけるような ひとときをあなたに。
giving you a sweet, melting moment.
ChocoLove
作詞・作曲 Junky
Lyrics/Composition: Junky
聞いて会いたいのもっとそばで
Listen, I want to see you more, closer by
少し困るくらいにおねだり
Asking for just a bit too much
ねえちゃんと聞いてみて受け取って
Hey, listen properly and accept it
甘くとろけちゃうような時を
A moment that will make you melt sweetly
疲れてる顔していつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You look tired, you're always working so hard
もう全て任せて全部食べてあげようか？
Shall I just take care of everything and eat it all up?
よそ見なんて嫌だよちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
I hate it when you look away, you have to face me properly
目と目が合うでしょ照れちゃうくらい見つめてね
Our eyes will meet, right? Stare at me until you're blushing
ひとつギュフにさせて
One, let me make you go “gyufu”
ふたつ見っけってね
Two, find me, okay?
虜にしちゃうよ心拍数急上昇
I'll captivate you, heart rate rising rapidly
好きよ
I love you
痛いの痛いの飛んでけ
Pain, pain, go away
不安な顔より笑顔見せて
Show me a smile rather than a worried face
ねえちゃんと聞いてみて受け取って
Hey, listen properly and accept it
甘いチョコのような時を
A moment like sweet chocolate
ここに痛いの痛いのもう困っちゃう
The pain is right here, it's so troubling
不意打ちにちょこっとときめく
My heart flutters just a bit from a surprise attack
散らしちゃうわよためもっとちょっと
I'll scatter them about, just a bit more of your “tame”
君の声をもっと聞かせて
Let me hear your voice more
不安なんて抱えてらしくないなんて思ってた
I thought it wasn't like you to be carrying such anxieties
全部全部丸ごと包み込んで溶かしてあげる
I'll wrap it all, every bit, up and melt it for you
どうしたって
No matter what,
何したって
no matter what I do,
気持ちは同じなんだね
our feelings are the same, aren't they?
ここだって
Even here,
どこだって
even everywhere,
思いは伝わるから
my thoughts will reach you.
声にして
Give it a voice,
文字にして
put it in writing,
勇気出して「好き」って伝えてよ
take courage and tell me "I love you."
今日だって
Even today,
いつだって
even always,
あぁ 愛し返すの
Ah, I'll love you back.
隠さないで ちゃんと教えて
Don't hide it, tell me properly.
君のこと 全部を
Everything about you...
ちょうだい
Give it to me.
今 会いたいの 飛んでって
I want to see you now, fly to me.
少し困るくらいに おねだり
Be a little troublesome and beg.
高鳴る心 聞いてみて
Listen to my racing heart.
感じてほしいの
I want you to feel it.
会いたいはすぐ 飛んでって
The "I want to see you" will fly immediately.
少し困るくらいに おねだり
Be a little troublesome and beg.
めちゃときめいて 受け取って
Be super thrilled and receive it.
甘くとろけちゃうような時間を
A time that feels like it's melting sweetly...
隣にいたいから
Because I want to be by your side.
みんなー！今日は来てくれてありがとうー！
Everyone! Thank you for coming today!
どうも、癒月ちょこ活動4周年記念ライブ、
Hello, I'm Yuzuki Choco, thank you for watching
見ていただいて、みんな、盛り上がってるー！？
my 4th anniversary live, is everyone getting excited!?
いや、オープニングはね、ちょこ、ちょこのね、
Well, for the opening, Choco...
オリ曲2曲、歌っちゃったんだけど、
I sang two of my original songs,
どうだった？やっぱちょこのオリ曲、
how was it? Everyone likes Choco's original songs,
みんな好きだよね？ちょこは大好き。
right? Choco loves them.
はい、ということでね、今回は、歌ライブ。
Yes, so, this time it's a singing live.
ちょっとね、前回味しめて、2回目やっちゃおうかなーと思って、
Since the last one was so good, I thought I'd do a second one,
企画してみたんだけど。この後はね、みんなを呼んで、
and I planned this. After this, I'll call everyone,
みんなと一緒に、色々ね、歌うので、
and I'll be singing various songs with them, so
ぜひぜひ皆様、このまま盛り上がっていくぞー！
everyone, let's keep this excitement going!
それでは、みんなのこと呼んでくるから、ちょっと待っててね。
Now, I'm going to call them over, so please wait a moment.
今日から君の好きなところ
From today, I'll tell you
1日1個伝えよう
one thing I like about you every day.
365回 ドキドキさせちゃうぜ
365 times, I'll make your heart race.
バッキュン！
Bang!
こっちにおいでよ もう
Come over here already.
もしかして まだ片思い？
Could it be it's still one-sided?
たまに甘えてくるくせに
Even though you act spoiled sometimes,
もしかして 転がされてる？
could it be I'm being played?
一目惚れして 毎日通ってた
I fell in love at first sight and came every day.
君と目が合うたびに
Every time our eyes meet,
恋が爆発！
my love explodes!
今日から君の好きなところ
From today, I'll tell you
1日1個伝えよう
one thing I like about you every day.
365回 ドキドキさせちゃうぜ
365 times, I'll make your heart race.
バッキュン！
Bang!
ほかのコは見たり
Looking at other girls?
携帯ばっか見たり
Looking only at your phone?
君だけ見てるよ
I'm only looking at you.
えらいコのご褒美は
The reward for a good boy is...
チュッ！
Chu!
たまにはお出かけどう？
How about going out once in a while?
いつも部屋デートばかりじゃん
We always just have dates in our rooms.
もちろんそれでもいいけど
Of course, that's fine too, but
僕だっておしゃれしたいし
I want to dress up too.
気分屋な君に
To you, who is moody...
汗輝いてるな
Sweat is shining
僕がいないと何も
Even though you can't
できないくせに
do anything without me
毎日君の機嫌とって
Every day I try to cheer you up
1日いっぱいハグして
Hugging you all day long
何百回何千回愛を伝えちゃうぜ
I'll tell you I love you hundreds, thousands of times
バッキュン！
Bang!
1人になっちゃったり
Sometimes getting lonely
ゲームばっかしたり
Or just playing games
君だけ見てるよ
I'm only looking at you
偉い子 ご褒美は
Good kid, the reward is...
チュ！
Chu!
帰り遅くなりそうだけど
I might be home late, but
急いで帰るからね
I'll hurry back
寄り道せず愛の巣 ただいま
Going straight back to our love nest, I'm home
お帰りもなし
No "Welcome home"
よしよしもなし
No "There, there"
それでもいいよ
Even so, it's fine,
だから一緒にいてね
so stay with me
ねーねー どこ隠れてるの？
Hey, hey, where are you hiding?
もしかして出て行っちゃった？
Could it be you left?
急に飛び付いてきた
You suddenly jumped at me
君は小悪魔だね
You're a little devil, aren't you?
今日から君の好きなとこ
From today, the things I like about you
1日1個伝えよう
I'll tell you one every day
365回ドキドキさせちゃうぜ
I'll make your heart race 365 times
バッキュン！
Bang!
他の子見たり
Looking at other girls
携帯ばっか見たり
Or just looking at your phone
君だけ見てるよ
I'm only looking at you
偉い子 ご褒美は
Good kid, the reward is...
チュ！
Chu!
はーい！ということで ういママ！
Hi! So, Ui-mama!
4周年おめでとう！
Happy 4th Anniversary!
ありがとー！イエーイ！おめでとう。
Thank you! Yay! Congratulations.
呼んでくれてありがとう。
Thank you for inviting me.
えー ういママと3Dできるのちょこ嬉しい！
Eh, Choco is so happy to do 3D with Ui-mama!
ポコピーぶり！
Since PokoPea!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
でもこのステージ初めて？
But is this your first time on this stage?
初めてです。
It's my first time.
お邪魔します。お邪魔します。
Excuse me for intruding.
うちのういをよろしくお願いします。
Please take care of our Ui.
失礼します。失礼します。
Excuse me.
すごいステージだね。びっくりしたよ。
What an amazing stage. I was surprised.
ね。見て見てここ。ロゴあるんだよ今日。
Right. Look, look at this. There's a logo today.
めっちゃ可愛い！イラストもめっちゃ可愛い！
Super cute! The illustration is super cute too!
ね。ゆづるちゃんありがとう。
Right. Thank you, Yuzuru-chan.
いやいや。こちらこそありがとうございました。
No no. Thank you as well.
いやー 一緒に歌って踊れる日が来るとは。
Man, to think the day would come when we could sing and dance together.
そう、ちょこもさ...
Yeah, Choco also...
4周年呼んだら来てくれるかなー ワクワクって思ってさ。
I was wondering, "If I invite her for the 4th anniversary, will she come?" I was so excited.
誘われて「あ、行く行く」っつって。軽いノリで来ちゃったね。
I was invited and said, "Oh, I'll go, I'll go." I came with a light heart.
めっちゃね。即答でね、返信きたよ。
Totally. I got an instant reply.
おお！？って。ちょこ緊張してたの返事くるまで。
I was like "Oh!?" Choco was nervous until the reply came.
「あ、行く行く」っつって。
"Oh, I'll go, I'll go," I said.
いや、もうそんな記念すべきね、ステージに呼んでいただけるなんて、もうそれはもう頑張るしかないですよ。
No, to be invited to such a memorable stage, I have no choice but to do my best.
え、もうめちゃめちゃ可愛かったよねみんな！
Eh, everyone was super duper cute, right!
大丈夫でしたか？
Was it okay?
きゅんきゅんだった。
It was heart-fluttering.
あー良かった。頑張って練習した甲斐あったわ。
Ah, good. It was worth the hard work practicing.
ね。ダンス頑張ってたもんねういママ。
Right. You worked hard on the dance, Ui-mama.
ちょこ先生は余裕ですね。さすがこれが4周年ってやつですか。
Choco-sensei is so relaxed. As expected of someone at their 4th anniversary.
いや 4年やってるんで。
Well, I've been doing this for 4 years.
格が違うわ。
The level is different.
はい。ということで。
Yes. So anyway.
せっかくだからちょこ、ういママに、ういママにお願いがあるんだ。
Since we're here, Choco has a favor to ask of Ui-mama, of Ui-mama.
え、もう私やること終わったから帰るわ。
Eh, my job is done so I'm going home.
あの、あの。最後に記念写真撮ってもらっていいですか？
Um, um. Could we take a commemorative photo at the end?
あ、はい。
Oh, yes.
もう、なに。帰る気満々じゃんね。
Geez, you're so ready to leave.
もうやることないのかなって思って。
I thought there was nothing left to do.
あるある。何ですか何ですか。
There is, there is. What is it, what is it?
それ、それ、写真撮りたい。それ、撮りたい。
That, that, I want to take a photo. That, I want to take it.
あー はいはい。
Ah, okay okay.
赤ちゃん、赤ちゃん、赤ちゃん。
Baby, baby, baby.
なな、なんて？何をしてほしいって？
Wh-what? What do you want me to do?
え、サムネのポーズ撮りたい。
Eh, I want to do the pose from the thumbnail.
えー
Eh...
めっちゃ嫌そうじゃんね。
You look like you really hate it.
ねー。
Right.
なんか違うんだけど。
Something's different.
なんか違う。
ういのほうから来てくれるの待って。
Wait for Ui to come to me.
あー
Ah...
ういのほうから来てくれるの待って。あーそんななでなで。
Wait for Ui to come to me. Ah, such head-patting.
4周年の角。
The 4th anniversary horns.
おい。おい。こら、うい。待って待って。
Hey. Hey. Hey, Ui. Wait wait.
やばいやばい。
Oh no, oh no.
おいおいおい。こういうことしてていいの？
Hey hey hey. Is it okay to be doing this?
ごめんなさい。一応ライブなんだよね。
Sorry. It is a live performance after all.
そうだよ。
That's right.
まだまだあるんでしょ？
There's still more, right?
だから。
So.
頑張れるように。
So I can do my best.
今から、可愛い応援がほしいなーなんて。
Right now, I want a cute cheer or something.
頑張れ！
Do your best!
うぇ。
Ugh.
頑張れ！
Do your best!
うぇ。
Ugh.
頑張れ頑張れ頑張れ！
Do your best, do your best, do your best!
というわけで、イラストレーターのしぐれういでしたー！
So, it was illustrator Shigure Ui!
じゃあ、最後に一緒に！
Then, one last time together!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
頑張ってね！
Good luck!
この後も頑張るちょこ、見てるよー！
I'll be watching Choco do her best for the rest too!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
作詞・作曲: Junky
Lyrics/Composition: Junky
全力で　GO！
With all our might, GO!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
全速前進　進め！
Full speed ahead, advance!
1、2、3！
1, 2, 3!
気合入れて (ホイッ)
Get fired up (Hoi!)
頑張って (ホイッ)
Do your best (Hoi!)
張り切りすぎて空回り
Getting too pumped and spinning my wheels
「問題なしっ」ってこっそりと (ちょこちょこ)
Secretly saying "No problem" (Bit by bit)
フォローするとかズルいズルい
It's unfair of you to follow up on me
何たって毎日がそんなまどろっこしくて
After all, every day is so frustratingly slow
目が回るようなハッピーデイ
A dizzying happy day
不器用なくらい直進的
Straightforward to the point of being clumsy
直進的でいい
Straightforward is fine
くすぐったいこの気持ちは何なのリ
What is this ticklish feeling?
せーので 嗚呼さんざんな今日だって
Ready, set, go! Even on a terrible day like today
きっと笑っちゃえばニッと
If you just laugh, you'll be grinning
ほら大丈夫で
See, it's fine
まだまだこんなん想定内だよ
This is still within expectations
踏んだり蹴ったり 意外とほんのちょっと頼れて
One misfortune after another, but surprisingly I can rely on you
困りまーす！ 困りまーす！
I'm in trouble! I'm in trouble!
晴れの日だって 雨の日だって
On sunny days, on rainy days
進めゴーフレフレ　毎度なれっごー！　誓いし
Forward, go! Fure fure! Every time let's go! I swore it
退屈ばかりならいいのに
I wish it were just boredom
今日は今日で今日で笑顔で頑張りましょう
Today is today, let's do our best with a smile
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
全力で　GO！
With all our might, GO!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
全速前進　進め！
Full speed ahead, advance!
1、2、3！
1, 2, 3!
嬉しくて (イエーイ！)
I'm so happy (Yay!)
ハイタッチ (ハイ！)
High touch (Hi!)
思わず微笑む昼下がり (しししっ)
Unintentionally smiling in the early afternoon (Hehehe)
タイミング (丁半)
Timing (Even or odd)
バッチリで (きまった！)
Perfectly (Decided!)
息止め慌てはずいはずい
Holding breath, flustered, so embarrassing
案の定 子供扱いしない　頭撫でたりもしない
As expected, don't treat me like a child, don't pat my head
勘違いしちゃうような大失敗
A big failure that might lead to a misunderstanding
ドキドキしちゃうくらい
Enough to make my heart throb
酔いすぎたかな？
Did I get too drunk?
ドレミで口を滑らせちゃうの (はいっ、あーん！)
Letting my tongue slip with Do-Re-Mi (Here, say ahh!)
ルンルンな毎日がいいな でも泣いちゃう時きっと
I want every day to be cheerful, but when I cry
お別れとか考えてパニックなっちゃうみたい
I seem to panic thinking about saying goodbye
愚痴なんか聞いてくれて ほんのちょっと勘違いしちゃいます
You listen to my complaints, and I misunderstand just a little
晴れの日だって 秋の日だって
On sunny days, on autumn days
頑張ってこれからだってもっと素直な私だしちゃう
I'll do my best to be more honest from now on
失敗なんか怖がらない
I'm not afraid of failure
今日は今日で最強です 明日も頑張りましょう
Today is today, it's the best. Let's do our best tomorrow too.
悔しいことも 嬉しいことも一緒に感じられる
We can feel both frustrating and happy things together
愛おしさんざんな日々が 甘いおしるこに溶けていく
The precious, terrible days melt into sweet oshiruko
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
全力で　GO！
With all our might, GO!
さんさんウィーク (ハイッ)
Sansan Week (Hi!)
全力前進 さんさんウィーク (ゴー！)
Full speed ahead, Sansan Week (Go!)
さんさんウィーク (ハイッ)
Sansan Week (Hi!)
全力前進 さんさんウィーク
Full speed ahead, Sansan Week
明日が好きでも 本当はお互い様ですが
Even if I like tomorrow, truthfully it's mutual
嗚呼さんざんな今日だって きっと笑っちゃえばニッと
Ah, even on a terrible day like today, if you laugh you'll be grinning
ほら大丈夫で まだまだこんなん想定内だよ
See, it's fine, this is still within expectations
踏んだり蹴ったり 意外とほんのちょっと頼れて
One misfortune after another, but surprisingly I can rely on you
困りまーす！ 困りまーす！
I'm in trouble! I'm in trouble!
晴れの日だって 雨の日だって
On sunny days, on rainy days
進めゴーフレフレ 毎度なれっごー！ 誓いし
Forward, go! Fure fure! Every time let's go! I swore it
退屈ばかり つまんないかもね
Just boredom might be dull
今日は今日で笑顔で頑張ろう
Today is today, let's do our best with a smile
一緒に頑張ろう 毎日楽しんじゃおう
Let's do our best together and enjoy every day
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
全力で　GO！
With all our might, GO!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
全速前進　進め！
Full speed ahead, advance!
1、2、3！
1, 2, 3!
アノーイング！さんさんウィーク！
Annoying! Sansan Week!
ちょこ先生！
Choco-sensei!
4周年おめでとうございます！
Congratulations on your 4th anniversary!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
いや、めっちゃめちゃ久々じゃない？お姉さん組で集まるの。
It's been a really long time, hasn't it?
For the Onee-san trio to gather.
もう知らない人もいるかもしれない。
There might even be people
who don't know us anymore.
我々ね、ASMRとかしてね、日頃癒しております、リスナーさんを。
We do things like ASMR to heal our listeners
on a daily basis.
お姉さん組、お姉三姉妹です。
We're the Onee-san trio, the Onee-three sisters.
これからももっと、いつかライブも出したいね。
I want us to perform at more lives together
again someday.
はい！ということでね、ちょこ4周年なんで。
Yes! So, since it's Choco's 4th anniversary...
ちょっと2人にお願いしたいことある。
There's something I want to ask you two.
ちょこ、2人に甘やかされたいなーなんて思っちゃってるんですけど。
Choco was thinking she wants to be
pampered by you two...
えー！もう全力で甘やかすよ！どんな風に？
Eh! We'll pamper you with all our might!
In what way?
2人の側、ああー！
By your side, ahh!
よしよし。毎日頑張って偉いね。
There, there. You're a good girl
for working hard every day.
大好きだよ。
I love you.
かわいいねー。
You're so cute.
幸せー！
I'm so happy!
ちょこ先生が膝から崩れ落ちてる。
Choco-sensei is collapsing from her knees.
いやでもね、本当にね、まだセクシーなんだよな。
But really, you know, she's still sexy.
崩れ方がちょっと誘ってるんだよな。
The way she collapsed is a bit inviting.
ちょこ先生まだまだあるでしょ？踊る。
Choco-sensei, there's still more, right? Dancing.
頑張ろう。ここで崩れ落ちてたら。
Let's do our best. If you collapse here...
まだまだあるよ！頑張れ頑張れ！もっと歌って踊るよ。
There's still more! Do your best!
We'll sing and dance more.
じゃあ最後に、ちょこが頑張れるエールを。
Then finally, give me a cheer
so Choco can do her best.
頑張れ、頑張れ、頑張れ、ちょこ先生！
Do your best, do your best, Choco-sensei!
ちょこ頑張るね！ありがとう！
Choco will do her best! Thank you!
よかった。恥ずかしくなってきたから帰ろう！
Great. I'm getting embarrassed, so let's go home!
バイバイ！頑張ってね！おめでとう！
Bye bye! Good luck! Congratulations!
デビきゅー、デビきゅー、デビきゅー、デビきゅーと！
Devi-kyu, devi-kyu, devi-kyu, devi-kyu-to!
よし、今日こそ決めるわ
Alright, I'll decide today
髪型チェック　スカートはたいて
Check hairstyle, brush off skirt
君に褒められる準備は万端
Ready to be praised by you
袖を掴んだらキュンとする？
Will you feel a 'kyun' if I grab your sleeve?
爪先触れたらドキッとするかしら
I wonder if your heart will throb
if our toes touch
可愛いって言わせちゃうくらいは完璧
Perfect enough to make you say I'm cute
今日の私は無敵なの
Today I am invincible
もはや天使や悪魔級にキュンと参っちゃうでしょ
Already angel or devil class,
you'll be enchanted by the 'kyun', right?
デビデビデビきゅー　デビきゅーと　クラクラさせるわ君のこと
Devi-devi-devi-kyu, devi-kyu,
I'll make you dizzy
デビデビデビきゅー　デビきゅーと　メラメラ燃えるこの心
Devi-devi-devi-kyu, devi-kyu,
this heart burns brightly
デビデビデビきゅー　デビきゅーと　君を振り向かせるためなら
Devi-devi-devi-kyu, devi-kyu,
if it's to make you turn around
デビきゅー　デビきゅー
Devi-kyu, devi-kyu
悪魔にだってなっちゃうわ
I'll even become a devil
デビきゅー、デビきゅー、デビきゅー、デビきゅーと！
Devi-kyu, devi-kyu, devi-kyu, devi-kyu-to!
手のひらすかせばギュッとする
If I peek through my palms, it feels tight
背中合わせたらソワソワするかしら
I wonder if I'll feel restless
if we're back to back
ドキドキ気付いてよ
Notice the heart thumping
気持ちも限界
My feelings are at their limit too
今日も私は素敵だよ
Today I'm lovely too
きっとミューズや悪魔級にキュンと参らせちゃおう
Surely like a muse or a devil,
let's make them fall for us 'kyun'
デビデビデビきゅー　デビきゅーと　フラフラしないで隣見て
Devi-devi-devi-kyu, devi-kyu,
don't stagger, look next to you
デビデビデビきゅー　デビきゅーと　キラキラしてるこの私
Devi-devi-devi-kyu, devi-kyu,
this sparkling me
デビデビデビきゅー　デビきゅーと　君を釘付けにできるなら
Devi-devi-devi-kyu, devi-kyu,
if I can keep your eyes glued to me
デビきゅー　デビきゅー
Devi-kyu, devi-kyu
悪魔にだってなっちゃうわ
I'll even become a devil
なのにズルいわそんな笑顔で
Yet it's unfair with that kind of smile
「おはよう」なんて言われたら
If you say something like "Good morning"...
プラン白紙
Plan back to square one
しらじら肌は
My pure white skin
舞っちゃうなー！
Is dancing!
デビデビデビきゅー デビきゅーと
Devi-devi-devi-Q, with a Devi-Q
クラクラさせるわ 君のこと
I'll make you dizzy for me
デビデビデビきゅー デビきゅーと
Devi-devi-devi-Q, with a Devi-Q
メラメラ燃える この心
This heart is burning bright
デビデビデビきゅー デビきゅーと
Devi-devi-devi-Q, with a Devi-Q
君を振り向かせるためなら
If it's to make you look my way
デビきゅー デビきゅー
Devi-Q, Devi-Q
悪魔にだって変身するわ
I'll even transform into a devil
デビきゅー
Devi-Q
デビきゅーと！
With a Devi-Q!
はい！ということで！
All right! And with that!
チョコさん4周年おめでとう！
Choco-san, congrats on your 4th anniversary!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとー！すごい！
Thank you! That was amazing!
あれ？今日なんか清楚じゃない？トワ様。
Wait, wasn't Towa-sama kind of pure today?
ええ、可愛いでしょ？ほら。
Eh? Wasn't I cute? Look.
珍しかったっすね、なんかトワ様がこういう曲歌うの。
It was rare for Towa-sama to sing a song like this.
あのさ、なんでこの曲選んだの？
Hey, why did you choose this song?
いや、これ悪魔組でなんか歌いたいなって思って。
Well, I wanted to sing something with the Devil Group.
最初可愛い曲かかっこいい曲かでめちゃめちゃ迷ったのチョコ。
I was really torn between a cute song or a cool one.
このメンバーだし、かっこいい曲も絶対合うけど、
With these members, a cool song would definitely fit,
でも絶対トワ様歌わない可愛い曲を、
but I thought I'd invite you to sing a cute song
なんか自分じゃ歌いにくそうだからチョコがお誘いして一緒に歌いたいなーって思って。
that Towa-sama usually wouldn't sing on her own.
えー、マジで嫌だったマジで。何がデビきゅーだよ！
Ugh, I seriously hated it. What's with 'Devi-Q'!
トワ様チョコ先から誘われて、普通に「いいよ」って言った？ラプラスは。
Towa-sama was invited by Choco-sen and just said 'okay.' How about you, La+?
あ、もちろん！即攻返してました。
Oh, of course! I replied instantly.
「いいですね！」って。ういー！みたいな。
I was like, 'Sounds good!' or 'Yay!'
トワは一回渋ったよね？
Towa, you hesitated at first, didn't you?
いや、ちょっと、本当にこれでいいの？この曲でいいの？みたいな。
Well, I was a bit like, 'Are you really sure? Is this song okay?'
いやでも、デビルだからぴったりですよ！
But it's perfect because we're devils!
そうそうそう、デビルで多分選んでくれてて、一緒に歌ってくれてるのはわかったから。
Yeah, I understood that you chose it with 'devil' in mind and sang it with us.
しかもチョコ先のね、記念だから、いや、歌うか。
Besides, it's Choco-sen's anniversary, so I had to sing it.
やばー！なんかかっこよかったし可愛かったですね。
Wow! It was both cool and cute.
え、そうなの？そうなの？
Oh, really? Is that so?
本当にチョコこれ欲望のままで選んだメンツだからね。
I really chose this lineup based purely on my own desires.
初めて歌ってめちゃめちゃチョコニヤニヤしちゃった。ありがとー！
It was our first time singing together, and I couldn't stop grinning. Thank you!
チョコ先とトワ様初めてだから、すごい。
It was the first time for Choco-sen and Towa-sama, so that's amazing.
え、てか3人も初めてですよね？
Wait, it's the first time for all three of us, right?
そうなの。なんかここシナジーあるかな。
That's right. I wonder if there's synergy here.
デビル、デビル、デビル...
Devil, devil, devil...
でもこの中だったら吾輩が一番角でかいし、一番偉い。
But among us, I have the biggest horns, so I'm the highest rank.
え、位でいうとどうなの？
Eh? What about our actual ranks?
位でいうと、トワはチョコ先の下だよ。
Rank-wise, Towa is below Choco-sen.
だって小悪魔だから。チョコ先の方がやっぱ大悪魔だから。
Because I'm a low-ranking devil. Choco-sen is an archdevil.
や、でもじゃあそんな悪魔の吾輩の方が角でかいから吾輩が一番偉いから。
Well, even so, I have bigger horns, so I'm the most important one.
チョコ先一番...ちんまりしてるしね。一番下かな。吾輩が一番！
Choco-sen is the smallest... so she's the lowest. I'm number one!
はいということで！
All right, moving on!
なんで！
Why?!
はい、じゃあ最後にチョコからお二人に、お願いがあるの。
Okay, finally, Choco has a request for both of you.
なーに？なーに？
What is it? What is it?
悪魔組だから、やっぱり皆様を誘惑したいなーって思って、
Since we're the Devil Group, I'd like to seduce everyone,
3人で誘惑ポーズして終わりたいなーなんて思うんだけど。
so I was thinking we could all strike a seductive pose together.
誘惑ポーズね。ポーズだったらまあ、まあまあまあ。
A seductive pose, huh? If it's just a pose, then I guess it's fine.
え、本当ですか？トワ様いいんですか？
Oh, really? Is that okay with you, Towa-sama?
いいよ、ちょっと我慢してやろうかなって思って。
Sure, I'll put up with it just this once.
足、足、足！チョコ先生ナイスすぎ今。
Legs, legs, legs! Choco-sensei, you look great right now.
え、いいかな？いいかな？
Is it okay? Is it really okay?
あ、まあじゃあ、誘惑ポーズですよね。
Well then, it's the seductive pose, right?
誘惑ポーズ行きますよ。カメラさん寄って寄って。
Here comes the seductive pose. Camera, zoom in, zoom in!
せーのでやりますよ、せーので。
Let's do it on the count of three.
渾身のやつ、渾身のやつ！
Give it your all, give it your all!
渾身の一発。
Our very best one.
せーの！
One, two, three!
もうやだー！トワ様かっこよすぎて！
Oh, no! Towa-sama is just too cool!
え、終わり？
Wait, is that it?
イカサマ⇔カジノ
Cheat Casino
作詞・作曲 ひとしずく×やま△
Lyrics & Composition by Hitoshizuku x Yama△
欲望　喧騒　駆け引き　渦巻くアンダーシティ
Greed, noise, and tactics swirling in the Undercity.
仕事　成功　夢希望　求める猛者たち
Work, success, dreams, and hopes sought by the fierce.
満天ディーラーギャンブラー　集まるカジノで
Dealers and gamblers gathered under a full sky at the casino.
あなたの大事なモノ　全部賭けましょう
Let's bet everything you hold dear.
今宵のGameは何だい？
What's the game tonight?
ほどよい刺激を頂戴
Give me some moderate excitement.
ホイール回してボール落とす　簡単なゲーム
Spin the wheel and drop the ball, such a simple game.
メランコリーなんて　退屈すぎるわ
Melancholy is just too boring.
狙うは36倍
Aiming for 36 times the payout.
さあ　二人のステージへ
Now, to the stage of the two of us.
行くよ？
Shall we go?
いいよ？
I'm ready.
目にも留まらぬ神業で　Show Time!!
With god-like skill faster than the eye can see, Show Time!!
運命的なシチュエーションで　遊戯盤は廻り出す
In a fateful situation, the game board begins to spin.
完敗　失うのは　金かプライドか？
Complete defeat. Is it money or pride you lose?
瞳を閉じたその隙に　心ごと奪ってあげましょう
In the gap when you close your eyes, I'll steal your whole heart.
羨望　幻想　溜息　渦巻くアンダーシティ
Envy, illusion, and sighs swirling in the Undercity.
裏切り　翻弄　自己破産　破れた猛者たち
Betrayal, mockery, and bankruptcy for the broken ones.
成り金負け犬堕天使　掃き溜めのカジノで
Upstarts, losers, and fallen angels in the gutter of the casino.
あなたの大事なモノ　全部賭けましょう
Let's bet everything you hold dear.
今宵のGameは何だい？
What's the game tonight?
ほどよい刺激を頂戴
Give me some moderate excitement.
トランプ5枚だけ揃える　簡単なゲーム
Just matching five cards, such a simple game.
ブラフで攻めるなんて　退屈すぎるぜ？
Attacking with a bluff is just too boring, isn't it?
狙うはDeep Jackpotのみ
Aiming only for the Deep Jackpot.
さあ　二人のステージへ
Now, to the stage of the two of us.
行くよ？
Shall we go?
いいよ？
I'm ready.
目にも留まらぬ神業で　Show Time!!
With god-like skill faster than the eye can see, Show Time!!
運命的なシチュエーションで　遊戯盤は廻り出す
In a fateful situation, the game board begins to spin.
完敗　失うのは　夢かプライドか？
Complete defeat. Is it dreams or pride you lose?
瞳を閉じたその裏に　痛いほど刻んであげましょう
I'll carve it into you so painfully behind those closed eyes.
最後のゲームは何だい？
What is the final game?
イカサマだらけの勝敗
A victory or defeat full of cheating.
サイコロ・ロールを繰り返す　簡単なゲーム
Repeating dice rolls, such a simple game.
Odds Betで一杯　退屈すぎるわ
Full of Odds Bets, it's just too boring.
そろそろシロクロつけましょう
It's time to settle this once and for all.
二人の勝負へ…
To our match...
行くよ？
Shall we go?
いいよ？
I'm ready.
目にも留まらぬ神業で　Show Time!!
With god-like skill faster than the eye can see, Show Time!!
絶対的なシチュエーションで　遊戯盤は廻り出す
In an absolute situation, the game board begins to spin.
完敗　失うのは　神かプライドか？
Complete defeat. Is it God or pride you lose?
瞳を閉じる暇もない　心ごと崩してあげましょう
No time even to blink, I'll tear down your heart completely.
目にも留まらぬ神業で　Show Time!!
With god-like skill faster than the eye can see, Show Time!!
感動的なシチュエーションで　遊戯盤は廻り出す
In a moving situation, the game board begins to spin.
逆転　失ったのは　愛かプライドか？
A turnaround. Is it love or pride you lost?
瞳を閉じたその隙に　心ごと奪ってあげましょう
In the gap when you close your eyes, I'll steal your whole heart.
うわあー！
Whoa!
ちょこせーん！
Choco-sen!
るいさまー！
Lui-sama!
いや、今日はお呼びいただきありがとうございます。そしておめでとうございます！
Thank you so much for inviting me today. And congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いやー、もう、ちょこるい様とかっこいいちょこ衣装で歌いたいと思って。
I really wanted to sing with you, Lui-sama, in this cool Choco outfit.
いや、めちゃくちゃ嬉しい。今回「イカサマ⇔カジノ」ね、めちゃくちゃかっこいいから。
I'm so happy. 'Cheat Casino' is just so cool.
そう、めちゃちょこ好きな曲だからね、一緒に歌えてめっちゃ嬉しい。
Yeah, it's a song I really love, so I'm so glad we could sing it together.
やったー！
Yay!
いつも可愛いな、もうちょこせんは。
Choco-sen is always so cute.
いや、もうそんな…
Oh, stop it...
ちょっと今日のこの可愛くてかっこいい姿を、一緒にパシャリしてくれる？
Will you take a photo with me in this cute and cool outfit today?
もちろん！
Of course!
え、ちょっとるい様の映えスポット教えてもらっていいですか？
Um, could you show me your best photo spot, Lui-sama?
オッケーです。じゃあ行きましょうか。
Okay. Let's go then.
じゃあジャンプしていきますよ。せーの！
I'm going to jump. Ready? One, two...
ていっ！
Tei!
はい、こちらが映えスポットです。どうぞ！
Here's the photo spot. What do you think?
え、めっちゃかっこいい！
Whoa, it's so cool!
そう、私のねステージを選んでくれたので、ご紹介させていただきましたが。
Since you chose my stage, I thought I'd introduce it.
じゃあ、ここでやりますか？
Shall we do it here?
え、ピースで行く？
Should we do a peace sign?
あ、背中合わせがいい、背中合わせでじゃあ。
Oh, let's go back-to-back. Back-to-back then.
イエーイ！
Yay!
写真撮ってるかな、みんな。
Is everyone taking photos?
うーん...
Mmm...
や〜可愛い。
Yeah, so cute.
いつも料理ばっかり一緒にしてるから、歌うってめちゃくちゃ新鮮ですね。
We're always just cooking together, so singing is really refreshing.
確かに。
True.
え、みんなどうだった？どうだった？
Hey, how was it everyone? How was it?
どうだったかな？リッチチョコの歌、最高だったでしょう？
I wonder how it was? The "Rich Choco" song was the best, right?
歌も美味しかった？
Was the song delicious too?
で、何か、ちょこ先あるんですか、このあと？
So, Choco-sen, is there something after this?
あ、そう！せっかくだから、ルイ様にサプライズ用意したのちょこ。
Ah, yes! Since we're here, Choco prepared a surprise for Lui-sama.
お！なんだろう？
Oh! What could it be?
ちょっと上さ、行きますよ。
We're going up a bit.
はい。
Okay.
ルイ様も一緒に。オッケ？せーの！
Lui-sama together too. Okay? Ready, set!
てい！
Hop!
お！じゃん！ダーツだ！何ですか？ダーツゲームするの？今から。
Oh! Ta-da! It's darts! What's this? Are we playing a darts game? From now?
そうそうそう！ルイ様にこれからダーツゲームしてもらおうかな？って思って。
Yes, yes, yes! I was thinking of having Lui-sama play a darts game now.
お！やりましょうやりましょう！ぜひぜひ！
Oh! Let's do it, let's do it! Definitely!
あ、じゃ、じゃ、お願いします。
Ah, then, then, please.
え、何ですか？え、何？え、何ですかこれ？
Eh, what is this? Eh, what? Eh, what's this?
ブルはちょこ。
The bullseye is Choco.
え、ちょこのブルはじゃどこかな？
Eh, so where is Choco's bullseye?
あ、ここかな？あ、ここかな？どこかな？あ、全部触っちゃっていいのかな？
Ah, is it here? Ah, is it here? Where could it be? Ah, is it okay if I touch everywhere?
あたたたた！ああああああ！
Wait, wait, wait! Aaaaaaaa!
ただいま映像が乱れております。しばらくお待ち下さい。
The video is currently being disrupted. Please wait for a while.
雨上がりの虹も
The rainbow after the rain,
凛と咲いた花も
And the flower that bloomed with dignity,
色付き溢れ出す
Are filled with colors.
茜色の空
The madder-colored sky
仰ぐ君に
You're looking up at,
あの日恋に落ちた
That day, I fell in love with you.
瞬間のドラマチック
A moment's dramatic scene,
フィルムの中の1コマも
Even a single frame in a film,
消えないよ 心に刻むから 刻むから
Won't fade away, as it's engraved in my heart. Engraved...
君だよ
It's you,
君なんだよ
It's really you,
教えてくれた
Who taught me.
暗闇も光るなら
If even the darkness shines,
星空になる
It becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に
Turning sadness into a smile,
もう隠さないで
Don't hide it anymore.
煌めくどんな星も
For any twinkling star,
君を照らすから
Will shine upon you.
眠りも忘れて
Forgetting even sleep,
迎えた朝日が
The morning sky I faced,
やたらと突き刺さる
Pierces through me so much.
低気圧運ぶ
Bringing low pressure,
頭痛ため息
Headaches and sighs.
忘れる君に会えば
I forget them when I meet you.
静寂はロマンチック
The silence is romantic.
紅茶に溶けたシュガーのように
Like sugar dissolved in black tea,
全身に巡るよ
It circulates through my whole body.
君の声
Your voice.
君だよ
It's you,
君なんだよ
It's really you,
笑顔をくれた
Who gave me a smile.
涙も光るなら
If even the tears shine,
流星になる
They become shooting stars.
傷付いたその手を
That wounded hand of yours,
もう離さないで
Don't let go of it anymore.
願いを込めた空に
In the sky filled with wishes,
明日が来るから
Because tomorrow is coming.
導いてくれた光は 君だよ
The light that guided me was you.
つられて僕も 走り出した
Being pulled along, I also started running.
知らぬ間に クロスし始めた
Before I knew it, they started crossing.
ほら 今だ ここで
Look, now is the time, right here,
光るなら
If it shines...
君だよ
It's you,
君なんだよ
It's really you,
教えてくれた
Who taught me.
暗闇は終わるから
Because the darkness will end.
君だよ
It's you,
君なんだよ
It's really you,
教えてくれた
Who taught me.
暗闇も光るなら
If even the darkness shines,
星空になる
It becomes a starry sky.
悲しみを笑顔に
Turning sadness into a smile,
もう隠さないで
Don't hide it anymore.
煌めくどんな星も
For any twinkling star,
君を照らすから
Will shine upon you.
答えはいつでも
The answer is always
偶然? 必然?
Coincidence? Inevitability?
伝え選んだ道こそ 運命になる
The path I chose and conveyed will become my destiny
握り締めたその希望も 不安もきっと二人を
Even that hope I held onto and the anxiety surely will
動かす光になるから
Become the light that moves us both
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと
I'll make you
夢中にさせてあげるからね
Even more crazy about me
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
羽根を広げ
Spreading my wings
魔法をかけてあげよう
I'll cast a spell on you
君だけに
Only for you
POP STAR
作詞・作曲：平井 堅
Lyrics/Music: Ken Hirai
君に出会えた喜びと
The joy of meeting you and
君に会えない寂しさの
The loneliness of not being able to see you
両方を手に入れて
I've got both and
恋は走り出す
Love starts running
空も飛べない僕だけど
I can't even fly in the sky
孤独を歌う夜だけど
It's a night I sing of loneliness
その頬に微笑みを
If I could bring a smile
与えられたなら
To those cheeks
初めて君を抱きしめた瞬間に
The moment I hugged you for the first time
神様が僕に下した
The mission God gave me
使命は君だけのヒーロー
Is to be your one and only hero
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと
I'll make you
夢中にさせてあげるからね
Even more crazy about me
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
羽根を広げ
Spreading my wings
魔法をかけてあげよう
I'll cast a spell on you
I wanna be a pop star
君をぎゅっと
I'll hold you tight
抱きしめてあげるからおいで
Come here, I'll give you a hug
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
羽根を広げ
Spreading my wings
魔法をかけてあげよう
I'll cast a spell on you
君だけに
Only for you
隠していたいくらい闇も
Even the darkness I want to hide
君はそっと拾い上げて
You gently pick it up and
大切な僕なんだと
Saying that I'm precious
抱きしめてくれた
You hugged me
光へと続く道を歩いてゆこう
Let's walk the path that leads to the light
傷ついたこの右手は
This injured right hand is
君と手を繋ぐために
In order to hold hands with you
You're gonna be my pop star
僕をもっと
Make me
夢中にさせてよ微笑んで
Even more crazy about you, with your smile
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
その瞳で
With those eyes
僕に魔法をかけて
Cast a spell on me
You're my only pop star
僕をぎゅっと
Hold me tight
抱きしめたらもう離さない
If you hug me, I won't let go
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
その瞳で
With those eyes
僕に魔法をかけて
Cast a spell on me
今すぐに
Right now
恋に落ちたら誰もが誰かのpop star
When you fall in love, everyone is someone's pop star
神様が僕に下した
The mission God gave me
使命は君だけのヒーロー
Is to be your one and only hero
I wanna be a pop star
君をもっと
I'll make you
夢中にさせてあげるからね
Even more crazy about me
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
羽根を広げ
Spreading my wings
魔法をかけてあげよう
I'll cast a spell on you
I wanna be a pop star
君をぎゅっと
I'll hold you tight
抱きしめてあげるからおいで
Come here, I'll give you a hug
キラキラのpop star
A sparkling pop star
羽根を広げ
Spreading my wings
魔法をかけてあげよう
I'll cast a spell on you
君だけに
Only for you
おおー！ありがとう！
Whoa! Thank you!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Congratulations! Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
まさか本当にポップスターになってしまうとはね。
I never thought we'd actually become pop stars.
ね、何でポップスターだったんだっけ？
Right? Why did we go with 'POP STAR' again?
かっけーな俺たち。
We look so cool.
忘れるな忘れるな。
Don't forget, don't forget.
こいつが平井婆ちゃんとか言い出したんだよ。
This person started calling it 'Hirai-ba-chan'.
伏線回収だったんだ。
It was a foreshadowing payoff.
なんかちょっとでも思い出したくない思い出かもしれない。
Actually, it might be a memory I don't really want to recall.
眩しかったよ、眩しかったよ。
It was dazzling, it was dazzling.
でもね、本当に4周年おめでとうです、ちょこ先生。
But really, happy 4th anniversary, Choco-sensei.
ありがとう、ありがとう！一緒にいてくれて。
Thank you, thank you! For being here with me.
え、ありがとう、ありがとう。
Eh, thank you, thank you.
なんかちょっとあれだね、セレブリティな香りがするね。
It feels like we have a bit of a celebrity vibe, doesn't it?
本当？セレブっぽい？
Really? Do we look like celebs?
この二人めちゃめちゃセレブリティな香りするよ。
These two really have a celebrity vibe going on.
本当だ。なんか某姉妹みたい。
True. You're like a certain pair of sisters.
ねえ、なんかちょっとジワるんだけど。
Hey, that's actually a bit funny.
うちらと言ったらね、スバちょこるなと言ったらなんかこれっていうのがある。
When it comes to us, to Suba-Choco-Luna, there's *this* one thing.
ないよ！何？
No, there isn't! What is it?
変なイメージをつけるな、スバちょこるなに。
Don't give Suba-Choco-Luna weird associations.
その顔やめて、ルーナたん。
Stop making that face, Luna-tan.
ルーナたんが一番おもろいんだよな。
Luna-tan is definitely the funniest.
ここ見てください、ここ見てください。ありがとうございます。
Please look here, please look here. Thank you so much.
演出かよ、こいつ。顔強えー。
Is this a performance? Her face is too much.
夜見たらちょっとびっくりするタイプ。怖いよ、ルーナたん。
The type that would startle you at night. You're scary, Luna-tan.
ちょっと塩振るポーズとかできるんじゃない？
Can't we do a salt-sprinkling pose or something?
急にどういうこと？急に塩振り？
What do you mean all of a sudden? Suddenly salt sprinkling?
ちょこなんか違うくない？なんか違くない？
Choco, isn't that a bit off? Isn't it a bit wrong?
でもなんかね、塩は振ってそうな感じするもん。
But it does feel like you'd be sprinkling salt.
塩、どう？こう？
Salt... how about this? Like this?
いや何のポーズやねん、これ。塩振りポーズ。
What kind of pose is this? The salt-sprinkling pose.
はい、じゃあ皆さんそろそろ帰りまーす。
Alright, everyone's heading home now.
おめでとう！おめでとう！ちょこ先生おめでとう！
Congrats! Congrats! Congrats, Choco-sensei!
チョコお疲れ！おめでとう！
Good job, Choco! Congratulations!
はー、お待たせー！
Phew, sorry to keep you waiting!
ということで、ここで皆様に…
So, here for everyone...
二つ告知があります！
I have two announcements!
まず一つ目がー…
First of all...
ドドーン！
Ta-da!
なななんと！癒月ちょこ活動4周年記念グッズが発売開始されます！
Unbelievable! Yuzuki Choco 4th Anniversary commemorative goods are now on sale!
21時からね！
Starting from 9 PM!
こちら内容の方が、ドドーン！
As for the contents... Ta-da!
市川はる先生描き下ろしイラストのアクリルススマホスタンド！
An Acrylic Smartphone Stand with a newly drawn illustration by Ichikawa Haru-sensei!
そして、二つ目！
And, the second item!
な、なんと皆様お待たせいたしました！
Ta-da! Sorry to keep you all waiting!
お出かけはこれでずっと一緒だね。しょこらのぬいぐるみ、可愛い！
Now we can be together forever when you go out. The Shokora plushie is so cute!
そして三つ目は、いやこれ待ってた人いるんじゃないかな？
And the third one... I bet some of you have been waiting for this.
こちら、ちょこ先生のエプロン！
This is Choco-sensei's apron!
いや、ちょこっとクッキングとかね、リッチちょことかでチョコがいつも着てるエプロンです！
It's the apron Choco always wears in 'Chocotto Cooking' and 'Rich Choco'!
そして四つ目はー…
And the fourth one is...
まあね、作った料理を盛り付けるのは、もちろんこのミニプレート！
Of course, to plate the food you've made, you'll need this Mini Plate!
いやめちゃめちゃ可愛くないですか？
Isn't it absolutely adorable?
そして、ちょこの耳舐めASMR！
And, Choco's ear-licking ASMR!
じゃーん！ちょこ書き下ろし台本になってるので是非是非皆様…
Ta-da! It's a script written by Choco herself, so please everyone...
ハスハスしながら聴いてください！
Listen to it while panting!
まあね、今回もね、もちろん特典ございます！
And of course, there's a bonus this time too!
癒月ちょこ直筆サイン入りポストカードです！こちら箔押しメッセージもちゃんと付いてきます！
A postcard with Yuzuki Choco's handwritten signature! It also comes with a foil-stamped message!
今回はね、1枚1枚ちゃんとチョコ手書きでメッセージ入れるんで、あ、メッセージじゃないや、サイン入れるので！
This time, Choco will hand-write a message on each one... no, not a message, I'll be signing them!
チョコの直筆サイン、ペロペロしちゃってください！
Please feel free to lick Choco's handwritten signature!
そして、
And,
告知その2はー…
Announcement number two is...
このあとすぐなので、みんなお楽しみにー！
Coming right after this, so please look forward to it, everyone!
NoDistance
作詞・作曲・編曲：涼木シンジ (KEYTONE)
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Shinji Suzaki (KEYTONE)
言葉を並べては　皆フラレライバイ
You line up your words, and they all just drift away
理屈だなんてゴミ箱へ
Throw your logic into the trash
身に覚えあるんでしょう　嘘さ
You know exactly what I mean, it's all a lie
チクチク痛いのね
It stings, doesn't it?
エゴイズムに躍らされて
Danced around by egoism
むせ返る　アーメン　アーメン
Choking on "Amens"
自惚れきった悪魔でも
Even for a conceited demon
癒してあげましょう
I'll provide some healing
お目覚めですか？
Are you awake now?
ジン、ドン、ギィ、ドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
響かせて　ジン、ドン
Let it ring out, ding-dong
笑い合うハッ、ハッ、ふざけて
Laughing together, ha ha, just messing around
ジン、ドン、ギィ、ドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
鳴らせよ　ジン、ドン
Ring it out, ding-dong
止むのが先か　病むのが先か
Will it stop first, or will I fall ill first?
噛みつきはしないわ
I won't bite you
慰めもしないわ
But I won't comfort you either
私の物ね
You're mine now
明日の　No Distance
Tomorrow's No Distance
闇に紛れ　甘いチョコにトロけてく
Blending into the darkness, melting into sweet chocolate
錆びた鎖繋いで　手枷解いてく
Connected by rusted chains, undoing the shackles
仮の姿化けて　瞳を閉じて
Disguised in a temporary form, close your eyes
傷つくためなのね
Is it all just to get hurt?
エゴイズムに躍らされて
Danced around by egoism
むせ返る　アーメン　アーメン
Choking on "Amens"
間違えを待った　毒々しくても
Waiting for a mistake, even if it's poisonous
癒してあげましょう
I'll provide some healing
お求めですか？
Is this what you desire?
ジン、ドン、ギィ、ドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
狂わせ　ジン、ドン
Driving you mad, ding-dong
最期にハッ、ハッ、叫んで
In the end, ha ha, scream out
ジン、ドン、ギィ、ドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
迷わず　ジン、ドン
Without hesitation, ding-dong
冷める前に　口づけを
Give me a kiss before it cools down
ジン、ドン、ギィ、ドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
響かせて　ジン、ドン
Let it ring out, ding-dong
笑い合うハッ、ハッ、ふざけて
Laughing together, ha ha, just messing around
ジン、ドン、ギィ、ドン
Ding-dong, ding-dong
鳴らせよ　ジン、ドン
Ring it out, ding-dong
止むのが先か　病むのが先か
Will it stop first, or will I fall ill first?
噛みつきはしないわ
I won't bite you
慰めもしないわ
But I won't comfort you either
私の物ね
You're mine now
明日の　No Distance
Tomorrow's No Distance
はーい！ということでみんなー！
Alright! So, everyone!
今回のオリ曲、めちゃめちゃかっこよくないですか！？
This original song is super cool, isn't it?!
ということで、今回のこのオリ曲、なんと！
And so, for this original song, believe it or not!
本日、24時配信開始プラス！
It starts streaming at midnight today, plus!
24時に、そのオリ曲のね、MVが公開されるので、
At midnight, the music video for it will be released,
楽しみに待っててね！
So please look forward to it!
ふふっ、24時、集まってて。
Hehe, gather together at midnight.
それでは、オリ曲とグッズとかのURLも、
Now, the URLs for the song and the merchandise
概要欄チェックしてください！
Are in the description, so please check them out!
そして、本日は最後まで見ていただいて、
Also, thank you for watching until the end today,
ご視聴いただきありがとうございました！
And thank you very much for tuning in!
Thank you for watching, my cute students!
お疲れ様〜ん。
Good job everyone~.